Guide to the Walter Isard papers, 1938-1986.
Isard, Walter papers
- PEPS Vol 2 # 4 (Summer) UN Peace-Keeping Tokyo, after 1999? (Box 106, Folder 33)
- Paelinck Rotterdam paper May 28, 1995-June 1995, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 34)
- Perspective Notes on Future of Reg'l Science Dec 1994, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 35)
- Yaman, Saltzman Oct 1994 (Trade and Conflict: A Gravity Model Reformulation), 1994-1996 (Box 106, Folder 36)
- Tinbergen on Peace Economics August 1994, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 37)
- Calgary Paper, June 1994 Canadian Peace Economics, 1994? (Box 106, Folder 38)
- Japan ECAAR 1994 (Conversion Problems: Implications for Arms Exports to Developing Nations, and World Security), 1993-1994 (Box 106, Folder 39)
- Boston 1994 PSSI AEA Paper, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 40)
- Summary Paper Int'l RSA Conference Beijing, Oct 1993, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 41)
- Oct 1993 Int'l RSA Beijing-Proven Methods in Reg Sci, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 42)
- RSA Moscow Aug 1993, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 43)
- Peace Economics Lecture March 4, 1993 Cornell Graduate Students, 1993? (Box 106, Folder 44)
- Regional Science: The New World Order and Mexican Development in a NAFTA era, after 1993? (Box 106, Folder 45)
- OECD Paper Feb 1, 1993 Paris (Lessons from Arms Reduction), 1993-1994 (Box 106, Folder 46)
- Peace Economics March 1992 for McGraw Hill Encyclopedia, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 47)
- OECD Conference Feb 1, 1992 (Lessons in Arms Reduction), 1992? (Box 106, Folder 48)
- PSSI Pittsburgh Paper Nov 1992 (Revisiting the Conceptual Framework of Peace Science), 1992 (Box 106, Folder 49)
- UNAM-Mexico City Conference Oct 2-3, 1992, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 50)
- UNU Conference Paper Nov 4-6 1992-Tokyo (Global Industrial Relocation), 1992? (Box 106, Folder 51)
- Article 211 - Peace Economics: Future Directions and Potential Contributions to International Security, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Article 212 - Ciencia regional, el Nuevo Orden Mundial y el desarollo de Mexico en la era del Tratado de Libre Comercio (Regional Science, the New World Order, and the Development of Mexico in the era of NAFTA), 1993 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Article 213 - An Economic Analysis of the Costs and Benefits of Ending the U.S. Nuclear Testing Moratorium, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Article 214a - Peace Economics: A Beginning at Definition, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Article 215 - UN and Russian Policy Forces, Coproduction in Place of Arms Exports and Japan's Entry into the Security Council, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Article 216 - Lessons from Arms Reduction in OECD Countries, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Article 217 - Trade and Conflict: A Gravity Model Reformulation (in Turkey), [N.D.] (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Article 219 - U.N. Peacekeeping, Disarmament and Security in the 21st Centurty: Contributions by..., 1995 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- Article 220 - Regional Science in New World Order, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 9)
- Article 221 - Economic Cooperation Between the Koreas, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 10)
- Article 222 - The Use of the Analytical Hierarchy Process in Conflict Analysis and an Extension, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- Article 223 - On Financing and Reorienting the United Nations, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- Article 224 - Perspectives of a Political Geographer on the Future, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- Article 226 - A Cooperative Analysis Procedure for Use by Diplomats and Negiotiators: With a Proposed Step for Resolving Conflict on the Korean Peninsula, 1998-1999 (Box 107, Folder 14)
- Article 227 - Regional Science: Parallels from Physics and Chemistry, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 15)
- Article 227 - Regional Science: Parallels from Physics and Chemistry, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 16)
- Article 228 - Alonso as Scholar and the Future of Regional Science: Remarks Prompted by Professor Teitz, [N.D.] (Box 107, Folder 17)
- Article 229 - Further Thoughts on Future Directions for Regional Science: A Response to Fujita's Remarks on General Theory of Location and Space Economics, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 18)
- Article 229a - Some Research Directions for Regional Development and Cooperation and Some Unanswered Questions in RS, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 19)
- Article 230 - Agglomeration Analysis: The Outgrowth of a Gravity-Electromagnetic (GEM) Model, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 20)
- Article 232 - Formative and Early Years of the Peace Science Society (International), 1999 (Box 107, Folder 21)
- Article 233 - Methods of Peace Research and Peace Science, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 22)
- Article 234 - New Dimension of Regional Science Research, [N.D.] (Box 107, Folder 23)
- Article 235 - On Dynamics of Political Organization: Empire Emergence and Decay, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 24)
- Article 235 - On Dynamics of Political Organization: Empire Emergence and Decay, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 25)
- Article 238 - Historical Material on the Formative and Early Years of the Peace Science Society (International), 2000-2001 (Box 107, Folder 26)
- Article 232 (Published Copy) - Conflict Management and Peace Science Journal, Vol 18 No 1, containing Isard article Formative and Early Years of the Peace Science Society, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 27)
- Kashmir Stalemate Proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 107, Folder 28)
- Historical Material on the Formative and Early Years of the Peace Science Society (International), 2000-2001 (Box 107, Folder 29)
- Art and Science on Nuancing Conflict, with Particular Reference to Developed and Developing Nations, 2001 (Box 107, Folder 30)
- The Urgent Need For More Applicability in Peace Economics, 2001 (Box 107, Folder 31)
- Adding Applicability of Leontief's Monumental United Nations Studies, after 2000? (Box 107, Folder 32)
- The Old City of Jerusalem as a Tourist International Magnet: An Initial Proposal for a First Step Cooperation in the Middle East, 2003 (Box 107, Folder 33)
- The Future (Near and Far) of Regional Science, after 2003? (Box 107, Folder 34)
- Developing Mutual Improvement Joint Actions: A Need for Interdisciplinary Research, 2002 (Box 107, Folder 35)
- Jordan: West Bank Development, 2004-2006 (Box 107, Folder 36)
- Research Methods for Sustainability of Development of the Regions and Nation of Indonesia, 2002? (Box 107, Folder 37)
- PEPS Organization, [N.D.] (Box 108, Folder 1A)
- Instructions to Authors, [N.D.] (Box 108, Folder 1B)
- TOC: Vol 5 No 1, 1998-2000 (Box 108, Folder 1C)
  PEPS Journal
- TOC: Vol 5 No 2, 1999-2000 (Box 108, Folder 1D)
  Table of Contents of Volume 5. No. 2 (Spring 1999) for PEPS Journal
- TOC: Vol 5 No's 3, 4, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 1E)
  Table of Contents of Volume 5. No. 3 (Summer 1999) and No. 4 (Fall 1999) for PEPS Journal
- TOC & Announcements: Vol 5 No 1, 1998-1999 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  Table of Contents and announcements of Volume 5. No. 1 (Winter 1998-1999) for PEPS Journal
- Editor Raymond Dacey, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 3A)
  Note from Isard to Dacey
- Editor Judith McDonald, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 3B)
  Note from Isard to McDonald
- Steven Brams, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 4A)
  Correspondence regarding publication in PEPS.
- Klein, Larry, after 1999? (Box 108, Folder 4B)
  Resume and publications of Lawrence Klein
- Jacek Kugler, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 4C)
  Correspondence regarding article in PEPS.
- Gustav Ranis, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 4D)
  Correspondence regarding publication in PEPS. Floppy disk.
- Rafael Reuveny, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 4E)
- David Singer, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 4F)
- PEPS Article Requests, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 4G)
  Drafts of letters requesting articles for publication in PEPS to various scholars.
- Steven Brams (Article), 2000 (Box 108, Folder 5A)
  Correspondence. Article for PEPS: Game Theory: Pitfalls and Opportunities in Applying It to IR
- Jacek Kugler (Article), 1999-2000 (Box 108, Folder 5B)
  Article for PEPS: Extensions of Power Transitions: Applications to Political Economy
- Leontief (Article), [N.D.] (Box 108, Folder 5C)
  Article for PEPS: Disarmament, Foreign Aid and Economic Growth
- Gustav Ranis (Article), 2000 (Box 108, Folder 5D)
  Correspondence. Article for PEPS: North-South Conflicts and Their Management--Revisited
- Rafael Reuveny (Article), 2000 (Box 108, Folder 5E)
  Correspondence, floppy disk. Article for PEPS: The Trade and Conflict Debate: A Survey of Theory, Evidence and Future Research
- Saperstein (Article), 1999-2000 (Box 108, Folder 5F)
  Article for PEPS: Nuclear Weapon "Pits": Burn Them or Bury Them? A Richardsonian Energy Competition Decision Model
- Weida (Article), 2000? (Box 108, Folder 5G)
  Article for PEPS: Potential Savings from Reform of DOE Nuclear Weapons Stewardship and from Nuclear Stockpile Reductions
- Williamson (Article), 2000 (Box 108, Folder 5H)
  Article for PEPS: Modeling the Number of United States Military Personnel Using Artificial Neutral Networks
- W.I. Unfinished Paper (Innumerable Ways to Cope with, Mediate, and Resolve Conflict), [N.D.] (Box 108, Folder 6)
  Isard unfinished paper.
- North East RSA Conference Buffalo Sept 22-23, 2000, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  Miscellaneous conference information, program.
- Yale 2001 PSSI WI's Paper, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  Notes, transparencies, drafts.
- Joint PSSI, UK ECAAR Conference June 13-17-London, WI's Paper, 1999-2001 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  Miscellaneous conference information, programs, emails, correspondence.
- Peace Science ASSA Jan 2000-2001 WI Paper, 2000-2001? (Box 108, Folder 10)
- Adding Applicability of Leontief 2000-2001, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  Drafts of Isard/Chung paper: Adding Applicability to Leontief's Monumental United Nations Studies and original Leontief article.
- Indonesia RS Conference March 20-22, 2001, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  Conference brochure and program.
- RSA So. Carolina 2001, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  Conference program and information. Internet print outs.
- AEA Meetings Jan 2002 Papers and WI's ideas and Fischer's, 2001-2002 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  Lecture materials, correspondence, emails, notes, draft of Fischer paper.
- Binghamton Nov 8, 2003, 2003 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  Lecture materials, notes, charts.
- Methods of Interregional and Regional Analysis WI's book, 1996-2003 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  Isard's coauthored book: Methods of Interregional and Regional Analysis. Notes and edits of book. Lecture notes, transparencies. PEPS Journal Vol 3, No 4 June 1996. Miscellaneous correspondence. Isard resume.
- Isard Resumes, 1990-1997 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  Isard resumes and published papers. Isard entry in: Who's Who in America. Commencement program. Honorary degree information.
- ECAAR Correspondence, 1976-1997 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  Miscellaneous ECAAR correspondence, faxes. News article.
- Walter Isard: Mail and Messages PSSI Part 1, 1991-1993 (Box 108, Folder 19A)
  Miscellaneous PSSI newsletters, conference information, correspondence, and notes.
- Walter Isard: Mail and Messages PSSI Part 2, 1988-1991 (Box 108, Folder 19B)
- PSSI Meetings and Newsletters, 1992-1994 (Box 108, Folder 20)
- Binghamton, 1989-1991 (Box 108, Folder 21)
- Conference Locations PSSI, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 22)
  Miscellaneous PSSI conference planning, notes, and brochures.
- California, 1987-1989 (Box 108, Folder 23)
  Notes, correspondence, campus maps of UC Irvine and Berkeley.
- GRACE, ECAAR Miscellaneous, 1993-2006 (Box 108, Folder 24)
  Miscellaneous articles, GRACE (Global Resource Action Center for the Environment), World Academy of Art and Science, ECAAR, EPS, ASSA, and AEA correspondence, emails, and newsletters.
- NARSA/NARSC, 2006 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- NEPS Newsletters, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- O, 2000-2007 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Oh, Jinhwan, 2006 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- P, Q, 1998-2006 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Palmer, 2002-2006 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- R, 1999-2005 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- S, 1998-2004 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- Amartya Sen, 2000-2001 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- U, 2002 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Morgan, Jim, 2007 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- T, 1999-2004 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Evolutionary Game Theory Article, 2006 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Springer, 2003 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- X, Y, [N.D.] (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Z, 1998-1999 (Box 109, Folder 16)
- V, 2003-2004 (Box 109, Folder 17)
- W, 1998-2004 (Box 109, Folder 18)
- Middle East Relations, 1998-2008 (Box 109, Folder 19)
- RS 620 Basic Penn Lectures Part 1, 1965-1993 (Box 109, Folder 20)
- RS 620 Basic Penn Lectures Part 2, 1972-1992 (Box 109, Folder 21)
- Jan 2005 Lectures Econ 307, 1977-2005 (Box 109, Folder 22)
- Isard Lecture Materials, 1950-1999 (Box 109, Folder 23)
- Cioffi, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  Article
- Cole, 1986-1987 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Cumberland, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Czamanski, 1993-1996 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Dacey, 1990-1999 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Donaghy, 1981-1993 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Deger, 1982-1986 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Drennan, 1991-1997 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Duchin, 1979-1994 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- Dumas, 1984-1988 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Durfee, 1985-1987 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Eisner, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Epstein, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- Faber, 1987-1990 (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Ferng, Jiun Jiun, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 15)
- Flavia/Flavio da Cunha Rezende, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 16)
- Fontanel, 1993-1995 (Box 110, Folder 17)
- Forcey, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 18)
- Fujita, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 19)
- Gale, 1989-1990 (Box 110, Folder 20)
- George, Alexander, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 21)
- Gigengack, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 22)
- Gokey, Lana, [N. D.] (Box 110, Folder 23)
- Gold and Adams, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 24)
- Gronicki, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 25)
- Haffar, 1991-1994 (Box 110, Folder 26)
- Haynes, Kingsley, 1995-1996 (Box 110, Folder 27)
- Hewings, 1986-1997 (Box 110, Folder 28)
- Hewitt, 1991-1993 (Box 110, Folder 29)
- Hidayat, Tirta, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 30)
- Hirshleifer, 1982-1989 (Box 110, Folder 31)
- Horn, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 32)
- Intriligator, 1982-1991 (Box 110, Folder 33)
- Isserman, 1992-1994 (Box 110, Folder 34)
- Isard, Peter, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 35)
- Iwabuchi, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 36)
- Iwan, 1992-1996 (Box 110, Folder 37)
- Jones, Barclay, 1987-1990 (Box 110, Folder 38)
- Jensen, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 39)
- Kassinis, 1989-1997 (Box 110, Folder 40)
- Peters, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Prigogine, 1991-1993 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Puu, after 1988? (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Plotkin, after 1987? (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Rice, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Rosen, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Sachs, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Sawaragi et. al, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Sayers, 1990-1991 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Simon, 1962 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Smolensky, 1988 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Somit, after 1988? (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Thayer, 1972 (Box 111, Folder 13)
- Toffoli, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 14)
- Wilson, E.O., after 1973? (Box 111, Folder 15)
- Wolfram, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 16)
- Vollmer, 1988 (Box 111, Folder 17)
- PSSI Binghamton, May 5-6, 1989, 1987-1989 (Box 111, Folder 18)
- Retrospect, Prospect Stockholm RSA Aug 1988, 1988 (Box 111, Folder 19)
- Karlsruhe Conference Feb 1990 Funck Birthday, 1989-1990 (Box 111, Folder 20)
- Ohio State U. Conference PSSI Nov 1989, 1982-1989 (Box 111, Folder 21)
- World Models Paper NERSA Paper Oct 9, 1988 Ithaca NY, 1988-after 1990? (Box 111, Folder 22)
- RSA-Stockholm Summary Paper Aug 1988, 1988 (Box 111, Folder 23)
- Lösche Tage Aug 1988, 1988 (Box 111, Folder 24A)
- Heidenheim Sept 3 Losch Ring 1988 Paper, 1988-1989 (Box 111, Folder 24B)
- RSA-Europe Newsletter Stockholm Aug 1988, 1989-1988 (Box 111, Folder 24C)
- Tokyo Paper-Jt. ASRW World Academy Conference Aug 20-21, 1988, 1988 (Box 111, Folder 24D)
- Old Stuff-Unsuccessful with B. Burton Middle 1980's Cornell, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 24E)
- Correspondence May 1, 1984, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 25)
- ECAAR Miscellaneous Part 1, 1995-1996 (Box 111, Folder 26A)
- ECAAR Miscellaneous Part 2, 1993-1995 (Box 111, Folder 26B)
- ECAAR Miscellaneous Part 3, 1993-1995 (Box 111, Folder 26C)
- ECAAR Miscellaneous Part 4, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 26D)
- ECAAR Miscellaneous Part 5, 1991-1993 (Box 111, Folder 26E)
- RSA Newsletters and Conferences, 1987-1989 (Box 111, Folder 27)
- Cornell Peace Studies Program, 1991-1996 (Box 111, Folder 28)
- Schmidt, 1987-1991 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Sen, Amartya, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  Paper
- Science Press, 1989-1992 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Slater, 1997 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Thünen, 1990-1994 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Theory Center, Larry Lee, 1985-1990 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Taiwan-RSA, PRSCO July 1992, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- T, 1986-1999 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- Stevens, Ben, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 9)
- Snickars, 1991-1993 (Box 112, Folder 10)
- V, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 11)
- Yale University Press, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 12)
- World University, 1982-1991 (Box 112, Folder 13)
- Westview Press, 1987-1990 (Box 112, Folder 14)
- Wasty, [N.D.] (Box 112, Folder 15)
- Tucson, 1991-1992 (Box 112, Folder 16A)
  Conference
- Tuscon II, 1989-1994 (Box 112, Folder 16B)
- Tuscon III, 1990-1992 (Box 112, Folder 16C)
- Stopler's Paper and Discussion, after 1951? (Box 112, Folder 17)
- WI's Correspondence 1980-1987, 1986-1988 (Box 112, Folder 18)
- X, Y, Z, 1985-1996 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  Correspondence and Papers
- W, 1985-1998 (Box 112, Folder 20)
- Correspondence 1986-88, 1986-1987 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  Miscellaneous ASSA, AEA, PSSI, WI's publications correspondence, conference planning/programs, Peace Science course material, notes
- Abt, 1995 (Box 112, Folder 22)
- Adams, 1990-1995 (Box 112, Folder 23)
- Alexander, Marita, 1989 (Box 112, Folder 24)
- Ahmet, Yaman, after 1992? (Box 112, Folder 25)
- Anderton, 1989 (Box 112, Folder 26)
  Paper; also paper by Grobar and Porter
- Arias, 1995 (Box 112, Folder 27)
- Arrow, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 28)
- Aziz, Iwan, 1997 (Box 112, Folder 29)
- Ball, 1983-1984 (Box 112, Folder 30)
- Baum, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 31)
- Baumol, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 32)
- Bennett, 1974-1990 (Box 112, Folder 33)
- Benoit, after 1973? (Box 112, Folder 34)
- Bergstrand, 1984-1999 (Box 112, Folder 35)
- van Bergeijk, 1988-1995 (Box 112, Folder 36)
- Berthelemy, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 37)
- Biswas and Ram, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 38)
- Brauer, Jurgen, 1990-1991 (Box 112, Folder 39)
- Bremer, Stuart, 1989 (Box 112, Folder 40A)
- Bremer and Deutsch, after 1987? (Box 112, Folder 40B)
- Brams, 1994-1997 (Box 112, Folder 41)
- Carroll, Admiral, 1995 (Box 112, Folder 42)
- Chang, 1989 (Box 112, Folder 43)
- Chen, Hsiao-ching, 1994-1995 (Box 112, Folder 44)
- Chenery, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 45)
- Carla Chifos, 1989 (Box 112, Folder 46A)
- Chester, 1978 (Box 112, Folder 46B)
- Bennett, Jim, 1987-1993 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  Correspondence with publishers
- Ballinger, 1984-1989 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Basic Books, 1989-1991 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Blackwell, Basil, 1987-1995 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Boyce, D., 1985-2005 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Ashgate Publishing, 1996-1997 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Avebury Press-Gower House, 1995-2006 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- Avebury-Permissions, 1996-1998 (Box 113, Folder 8)
- B, 1985-1999 (Box 113, Folder 9)
- A, 1985-1997 (Box 113, Folder 10)
- Academic Press, 1992-1997 (Box 113, Folder 11)
- Avebury-Book, 1989-2005 (Box 113, Folder 12)
- PSSI Newsletter Aug 1988, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 13)
- Newsletter PSSI March 1988, 1987-1988 (Box 113, Folder 14)
- Newsletter PSSI March 1990, June 1990, Aug 1990, 1990-1993 (Box 113, Folder 15)
- PSSI Newletter Aug 1989, 1989-1991 (Box 113, Folder 16)
- PSSI Newsletter Feb 1989, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 17)
- PSSI Newsletter June 1989, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 18)
- PSSI Relocation-Shel Levy, 1987-1989 (Box 113, Folder 19)
- PSSI Jan 1987 Newsletter, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 20)
- PSSI Newsletter May 1987, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 21)
- Newsletter PSSI Aug 1987, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 22)
- Peace Studies-Peace Science Field-May 1987, 1984-2001 (Box 113, Folder 23)
- PS 307, PS 603, PS 507, CRP 495.18, 1992-2005 (Box 113, Folder 24)
- Graduate School Records, 1992-2001 (Box 113, Folder 25)
- Peace Science 1972-76 Miscellaneous for WI, 1969-1995 (Box 113, Folder 26)
- Peace Science Newsletters 1972-75, 1971-1976 (Box 113, Folder 27)
- PSSI Newsletters 1982-6, 1982-1987 (Box 113, Folder 28)
- Peace Studies Program, 1987-2002 (Box 113, Folder 29)
- Cornell-CRP-Goldsmith dated 1987, 1985-1994 (Box 113, Folder 30)
- Econ 603- Summer 93, 1993 (Box 113, Folder 31)
- College of Architecture, Planning, 1985-1991 (Box 113, Folder 32)
- RSA Niagara Falls Nov 1994, 1992-1994 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Calgary Conference June 1994-Canadian Economic Association, 1994 (Box 114, Folder 2)
- AEA Boston Jan 1994 Meetings, 1992-1994 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- Int'l RSA Conference Beijing, Oct 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- RSA Moscow Aug 1993, 1993 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- OECD Conference Paris, Feb 1-2, 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 6)
- AEA-1992-Jan 1993, 1990-1993 (Box 114, Folder 7)
- Dec AEA Atlanta 1992, 1988-1993 (Box 114, Folder 8)
- Pittsburgh PSSI Meeting Nov 13-15, 1992, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 9)
- Hague-Peace Palace Conference May 1992, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 10)
- Reg-Sci Summer Institute Taipei-July 1992, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 11)
- U.N.U. Conference Nov 4-6, Tokyo 1992 (Future Global Change), 1992 (Box 114, Folder 12)
- Rottersdam 4th World Peace Science Conference May 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 114, Folder 13)
- AEA-Nominations Committee Jan-April 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 114, Folder 14)
- AEA 1991-92, 1989-1991 (Box 114, Folder 15)
- ARSC-Dec 7-8- Conference 1991, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 16)
- Tokyo, Sept 17, 1991 Japan Center for Econ Research, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 17)
- Hokkaido, Japan 9/13/91, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 18)
- AEA-PSSI 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 114, Folder 19)
- Boston-RSA-Dinner in Honor of WI, [N.D.] (Box 114, Folder 20)
- Workshop, R.S. Summer Institute Indonesia July 1990, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 21)
- Nationalism-Peace on a Small Planet, Rotterdam, May 16, 1990, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 22)
- First PRSCO Summer Institute-Indonesia Bjarkata Workshops July 1990, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 23)
- Paper by WI (World Modelling on Consequences of Military Expenditures), after 1990? (Box 114, Folder 24)
- Royal Wedding Reception, Tokyo-July 1990-Seminar-U of Tokyo July 3, 1990, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 25)
- Karlsruhe-Feb 1990, 1988-1990 (Box 114, Folder 26)
- Illinois (Urbana) Workshops, Sept 1989, 1989-1990 (Box 114, Folder 27A)
- Illinois Workshop on Large-Scale Social Science Models, 1988-1989 (Box 114, Folder 27B)
- Applied Reg'l Science Conference Japan, Sakashita, Aug 1988, 1987-1988 (Box 114, Folder 28)
- PSSI-3rd World Congress June 1988, [N.D.] (Box 114, Folder 29)
- AEA-PSSI Paper Dec 1987 Chicago, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 30)
- RSA Nov Baltimore 1987 Super Computers & Big Models in Reg'l Science, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 31)
- PSSI Seminar, Nov 1987 Cambridge MIT, DDIR Conference, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 32)
- COPRED Conference, Milwaukee Nov 1987, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 33)
- WI Notes 1/15/88, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 34)
- Orani Lecture-U of Melbourne Aug 1987, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 35)
- Surfer's Paradise-Australian Econ Society-Aug 27, 1987, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 36)
- AEA-PSSI Meeting Dec 1987, Dec 1988, 1986-1990 (Box 114, Folder 37)
- PSIG-Trad Matrix Construction-Jan-July 1987 paper, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 38)
- Isard-Dean Paper & Materials Basic To-July 1986; June 1986-Institute of Royal Science Conference Umea; Aug 1986 Tokyo W U Meeting, 1986 (Box 114, Folder 39)
- European Economics Assoc Paper Vienna Sept 1986, 1986 (Box 114, Folder 40)
- AEA New York 1985 Dec, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 41)
- AAG-Minneapolis May 1986 Joint with PSSI, [N.D.] (Box 114, Folder 42)
- PSSI College Park Md-Nov 1985, [N.D.] (Box 114, Folder 43)
- Canterbury Paper PSSI Sept 1985, [N.D.] (Box 114, Folder 44)
- Stockholm-SIPRI-Oct 1985, after 1984? (Box 114, Folder 45)
- Reich, Robert, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  Articles
- Reppy, 1987-1991 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- ReVelle, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 3)
- Robinson, Roland-Holst, 1986-1996 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- Romanoff, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 5)
- Russett, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- Rose, 1989 (Box 115, Folder 7)